module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What state do the Belchers live in?',
  a: 'Maine',
  b: 'Massachusetts',
  c: 'New Jersey',
  d: 'Connecticut',
  answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is Tina’s middle name?',
  a: 'Celeste',
  b: 'Bertha',
  c: 'Ruth',
  d: 'Mary',
  answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which character is voiced by the only main female cast member?',
  a: 'Gene',
  b: 'Louise',
  c: 'Linda',
  d: 'Tina',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'When Bob and Linda opened up the house as a B&B, their first guest was Javed. What was his occupation?',
  a: 'Entomologist',
  b: 'Optometrist',
  c: 'Meteorologist',
  d: 'Geologist',
  answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What instrument does Gene always have with him?',
  a: 'harmonica',
  b: 'keyboard',
  c: 'drumsticks',
  d: 'maracas',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where does Bob finally find the Love-Testometer in the episode "My Fuzzy Valentine"?',
  a: 'Drink Dynasty Lounge',
  b: 'Peking Duck Dynasty Bar',
  c: 'The Great Bar of China',
  d: 'Emperor\'s Bar and Lounge',
  answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the purple store next to Jimmy Pesto\'s Pizzeria?',
  a: 'That\'s Notable Stationery',
  b: 'Yours Truly Stationery',
  c: 'Staples n Stuff Stationery',
  d: 'With Love Stationery',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What did the kids try to buy at Fig Jam that got them banned from coming in again?',
  a: 'Chocolate covered edamame',
  b: 'Black garlic',
  c: 'Artisan gummy bears',
  d: 'Dark chocolate with bacon and red pepper flakes',
  answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Regular sized Rudy is Louise’s BFF. What’s the name of the other Rudy?',
  a: 'Abnormally Large Rudy',
  b: 'Pocket Sized Rudy',
  c: 'Small Rudy',
  d: 'Medium Sized Rudy',
  answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who does Daryl dress up as for Halloween in the episode "Fort Night"?',
  a: 'A red crayon',
  b: 'Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson',
  c: 'Mark Mothersbaugh',
  d: '1980s era Michael Jackson',
  answer: 'c'
  }
];

